# RESUME



# EDUCATION

MAR 2009 - DEC 2014

# **Degree in Computer Science**

National University of San Juan - FCEFyN - ARG

Thesis still pending.
Current GPA: 8.6 of 10

MAR 2005 - DEC 2008

#### **Electronic Technician**

National University of San Juan - EIDFS - ARG GPA: 8.57 of 10.

# SKILLS

Javascript

Angular 9

React

NodeJs

Java

**Professional Skills:** Git, Unit Testing, Scrum, Iira, Leadership, Collaboration, Problem Solving.

### LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: Fluent, Professional working

proficiency

# **GONZALO TERZANO**

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Phone: (+549) 264 464 9709 | Email: gonzaloterzano@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/gonzalo-terzano | GitHub: www.github.com/gonzadk

#### ABOUT ME

I'm a 30 years old Sr Software Developer (with Frontend focus) from Argentina and currently based in Córdoba. I enjoy working on extensive teams and sharing my knowledge in order to help other people to achieve professional success. I am currently focused on improving my leadership skills and I am also an amateur basketball player.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

APR 2020 - Present

#### Frontend Developer

Raftr - Remote

Brief Description: Working as a Frontend Developer on a great startup focused on connecting universities and colleges with students. Working with React and NextJs

OCT 2019 - APR 2020

#### Software Engineer

24 Hour Fitness - Remote

Brief Description: I was in charge of rewritting a front-end project that allow clients to purchase memberships and add different ancillary products. Working with angular 9 and ngxs

JUN 2019 - SEP 2019

# **Full Stack Engineer**

ThirdLove - Córdoba, Argentina

Brief Description: I worked at Thirdlove redesigning one of the company's insignia app called FitFinder, that helps woman finding their best bra. We were developing a standalone application that runs with ReactJs and NodeJs

FEB 2017 - MAY 2019

# **S**oftware Development Engineer

McAfee - Córdoba, Argentina

Brief Description: Fullstack developer responsible for end-to-end app development. Leading three teams of 5-6 people each. Working also on an inner source library reducing considerable work time of multiple projects across the company.

FEB 2016 - JAN 2017

# Web UI Developer

Globant – Córdoba, Argentina

**Brief Description**: Worked on a busy team, sometimes under pressure, making friendly & interactive projects of eLearning on short periods of time.

APR 2015 - JAN 2016

# Full Stack Developer

TravelPAQ - San Juan, Argentina

Brief Description: Great startup Company in which I worked on backend and frontend technologies but where I also had to perform deployments and configuration tasks on the servers.